-- ==CMCT团队荣誉出品== --
字幕调校: 浪人情歌 影片压制: 虚无
招募Q号: 76846146
当我走上楼梯时
As I was going up the stair
我看到一个不在那里的人
I met a man who wasn't there
今天他又不在那里
He wasn't there again today
"第六次会诊" "病患:麦肯芮佛"
我希望...我希望他会永远消失
I wish I wish he'd go away
这是从哪儿学来的?
Where did you learn that?
那首诗是从哪儿学来的?
Where did you learn that poem?
我自己编的
I made it up.
我小时候乱编的
When I was a kid, I made it up.
你对小时候还有什么记忆?
What else do you remember from back then?
你就直接问吧 医生
Don't beat around the bush, doc. Don't beat around the bush.
快直接问吧 医生
Don't beat around the bush. Don't beat around the bush, doc!
你对你母亲有什么记忆?
Tell me what you remember about your mother.
"窃盗罪"
我记得我妈
I remember my mom.
"妨害风化罪" "违反假释条例"
我记得我妈
I remember my mom.
我记得她是个妓女
I remember my mom was a whore.
她都把你关在那儿多久?
How long would she keep you there?
她去忙多久就要多久
As long as she was busy.
"小男孩被遗弃在汽车旅馆"
"小男孩遭到遗弃及虐待"
佛州...
儿童寄养中心
你知道你为什么来见我吗?
Do you understand why you're talking with me now?
因为你专门治疗...
You're supposed to be good with...
"山区谋杀案"
头痛
...headaches.
"凶手麦肯芮佛被捕"
我吃普拿疼没有用 知道我说什么吗?
I need something more than aspirin. Know what I mean?
你记得那些谋杀案吗?
Do you remember the murders?
我记得...
I remember...
南卡州的首府是哥伦比亚市
...that Columbia is the capital of South Carolina.
我也记得...
I remember that...
分裂人格是...
邪恶的来源
你在1998年5月10日...
Are you the person who murdered six residents...
是不是杀死六名大楼住户?
...of the Lakeworth Apartments on May 10, 1998?
"知名精神科医师出庭作证"
那天是我的生日
That's my birthday.
"精神错乱辩护遭到驳回"
现在我在跟谁讲话?
Who am I speaking to right now?
"芮佛被求处死刑"
我该叫你什么?
What should I call you?
随便你怎么叫都行
Call me whatever you want.
盖瑞?
Gary?
盖瑞 你醒了吗?
Gary, you awake?
没错 我被你吵醒了
Yes, Greg, as a matter of fact, I am awake.
抱歉这么晚打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you at home...
但芮佛案要举行午夜听证会
...but there's gonna be a midnight hearing in the Rivers case.
辩方找到新的物证... 一本日记
The defense found a notebook misfiled in evidence, a diary.
他们指控检方蓄意隐藏证据
They argued to the state Supremes that it was suppressed.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
媒体都不知道 消息没有走漏
There's no media. This all happened under the radar.
囚车一小时前离开监狱
The prisoner transport left an hour ago from Ely.
什么意思? 哪来的囚车?
Left Ely? What do you mean? What transport?
辩方再度辩称被告精神错乱
The diary gave them an opening to argue insanity again.
他们要芮佛出席 于是让他服药坐上囚车
They need Rivers present, so they drugged him, put him on a transport.
这人渣在处决前...
They're taking this scumbag to a hearing...
要出席听证会
...the night before his execution.
你怎么会捅出这种大篓子?
How the fuck did you let that happen?
有人想再玩一回合吗?
Would anyone like to play another round?
"汽车旅馆"
打开另一个谜题 我们有什么?
Let's get another puzzle, Vanna. What do we have?
- 关于家庭用品 - 买一个母音
- "Around the House" is the category. - Buy a vowel.
- 买母音啦 - 请拿起旅游赠卷
- Buy a vowel. - Pick up that trip.
- 买母音啦 猪头 - 我要买一个母音 E
- Buy a vowel, you idiot. - I'd like to buy a vowel. An E.
一个母音 E
One E.
- 好的 你剩三百五十元 - N
- All right, 350 left. - N.
买一个母音
- Buy a vowel. - Buy another vowel.
- 对了 - I
- Yes! - An I.
- 我要解答 - 好的
- I'd like to solve. - Sure.
奇宝狗食
"Kibbles 'n Bits. "
她一直流血不止
She won't stop bleeding. She won't stop bleeding.
- 天啊怎么回事? - 发生车祸 我们出了车祸
- Jesus. What happened? - An accident. We had an accident.
内华达州豪雨成灾
Rain and lightning is moving into Elko.
气象局预测有一场豪雨
Doppler Radar has picked up a severe thunderstorm with lightning...
将从中北部袭卷全州
...on its way from Pershing and Lander counties.
- 将有暴风... - 4乘以10等于...
- We could get damaging winds... - Four times 10 equals...
4乘以10等于...
Four times 10...
提姆西 别吵 我们在听广播
Timothy, could you not do that now? We're trying to hear about the storm.
- 你要我来开吗? - 不用
- Sure you don't want me to drive? - No.
我先开到安德森市 吃过饭再让你接手
I'll get us to Anderson, then you can take over after we eat.
顺着打滑方向打方向盘
Turn into spin.
用力踩几次刹车
Apply brakes with short, firm pumps.
看一看照后镜和仪表板
Check mirror and gauge indicator and roll...
然后平顺缓慢地停车
...to a slow, smooth stop.
你没事吧? 提姆西呢?
You okay, honey? Timothy?
安全带...幸好有系安全带
Seat belts, seat belts, seat belts.
- 一只高跟鞋 - 什么?
- It's a shoe. - What?
我辗到一只高跟鞋
It's a shoe!
他是个大好人...
For he's a jolly good fellow
他是个大好人
这一点大家都知道
Which nobody can deny
可恶
Shit!
- 为什么不买好一点的备胎? - 好的备胎很贵耶 艾莉丝
- Why didn't we get a better spare? - Do you know what radials cost, Alice?
老公 别生气
Honey, don't get defensive.
如果想让孩子念好学校...
Well, if the point is to put him, Timothy, into the right school...
- 就不能花太多钱在... - 乔治...
- ...it's absurd to focus... - George? George?
- 备胎上 - 我能帮什么忙?
- ...on replacement tires. - What can I do to help?
不用了 我能搞定 不过...
Nothing. I'm fine, but...
谢谢你
...thank you.
我的天! 我的天 艾莉丝?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Alice?
老天 艾莉丝? 你干了什么好事?
Oh, my God! Alice? What have you done?
你干了什么好事? 你干了什么好事?
What have you done? What have you done?
嗨 哈利 我该从何说起?
Hi, Harry. Where do I begin?
我一气之下走出片场
I have walked off the set, okay?
我知道他们会说我违约
I know they'll say that I am in breach...
不过他们也没按照合约来
...but they clearly did not read my deal.
他们让我住连锁旅馆...
They had me at a Ramada...
我的天
Oh, Jesus.
我的袋子有备用电池
I think I have a spare battery in my bag.
什么?
Excuse me?
你旁边的袋子里有备用电池
I have a spare battery in my bag up front, next to you.
- 哪一个袋子? - 那个LV手提袋呀
- Any idea which one, Miss Suzanne? - The Louis Vuitton duffel, right on top.
我没看到
I don't see anything...
你是瞎了吗? 在侧袋里头 快找呀
Just use your fucking eyes! It's in the side pocket! Just look!
天啊
Jesus!
你干了什么好事?...
What have you done? What have you done?
你猪头呀 如果你帮他就脱不了关系
No, fool! If you help him, you assume responsibility.
这本来就是我的错 放开我
It is my responsibility. Let go of me.
艾莉丝?
Alice? Alice?
你干了什么好事?...
What have you done? What have you done?
让我看看她
Let me take a look.
汽车驾驶在行驶中...
The driver of every motor vehicle involved in any manner of accident...
涉及任何交通事故 应该在十天内...
...originating from the operation of a vehicle shall, within 10 days...
你车上有毛巾吗?
You got a towel or something in the car?
过来帮我找
Okay. Come help me look.
在车祸发生十天内...
... within 10 days of the accident...
汽车驾驶在行驶中 涉及任何交通事故...
...if you are operating a vehicle and it should, at any time, involve...
- 待在这儿 别让她淋湿了 - 不会有事 老婆
- Stay here. Keep her dry. - It's okay. It's okay, honey.
- 快开门 我要用手机 - 不要
- Open the door! We need the phone. - No!
老婆 没事了
Sweetheart, it's okay.
Honey, it's okay.
- 把你的手机给我 - 收不到讯号
- Give me the goddamn phone! - The phone is dead, all right?
医生会把你治好 你不会有事
You're gonna be fine. You're gonna be okay.
不!
No!
- 她一直流血不止 - 天啊怎么回事?
- She won't stop bleeding. - Jesus. What happened?
出了车祸 我能借用电话吗?
There was an accident. May I please use your phone?
- 我能借用电话吗? - 当然了
- Please use your phone? - Yeah, sure.
该死 一下大雨电话就不通
Shit. I'm not getting a line. It happens in the rain.
电话打不出去
The phone doesn't work.
往东走三十里是圣朱德医院
St. Jude's has 24-hour emergency, 30 miles east.
好的
Okay.
乖乖坐下来
You sit here, okay?
继续压着伤口 我去找救护车
Keep pressure on the wound. I'll be back with an ambulance.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
这里比连锁旅馆更糟 不过你得凑和凑和
Sorry. It's a step down from the Ramada, but it'll have to do.
我才不住在这儿 你疯啦?
I am not staying here. Are you out of your mind?
这是我的车 你是我的司机 快把袋子放回去
This is my car. You work for me. Get those bags back in this car now!
我知道她被车撞到一直流血 但我也是病人耶
I understand the bleeding person has a medical condition, but so do I.
我有支气管扩张症 我待在这儿会窒息而死
My lung walls have depleted cilia. If I stay here, I could asphyxiate!
不要熄火 拜托拜托...
No, please, please, please, please, please, please.
拜托!
Please!
喂!
Hey!
停车 求求你
Stop. Please, please.
我的车泡水了 能搭便车吗?
Hi. I'm sorry, my car is stuck. Can I get a ride?
好的
Okay.
""存在与虚无"沙特着"
你往东开去
You know you're going east.
我要去医院
Hospital's this way.
那儿淹大水 死路一条
It's flooded. I mean, it's a dead end.
没办法 我得试一试
Yeah, well, if you don't mind, I gotta try.
三十元付现
Okay, that will be $30 cash, please.
你以前不是那个大明星吗?
Didn't you use to be that actress?
没错
Yes.
这房间好不好?
- Wow. - Now, is that a nice room?
虽然我很快就走 不过我还是要好房间
Because though I am leaving soon, I still would prefer a nice room.
最舒服的房间
Your nicest...
请你帮帮忙
...if that is possible.
八号房很舒服
Eight's very cozy.
我早就跟你说了
I tried to tell you.
快停车 你过不去
Hey! Hey, stop! There's no way through.
There's no way through! No way through!
- 小路 醒醒 - 什么?
- Lou, wake up. - What?
手机
Cell phone.
- 什么? - 你有手机吗?
- What? - Do you have a cell phone?
你是谁呀?
Who wants to know?
有位女士出车祸受重伤
There's been an accident, a bad one. A lady's hurt.
- 我需要一支手机 - 朋友 放轻松
- We need a cell phone right now. - Dude, slow down.
老兄 我们又不认识你 也没看到有车祸
First, we don't know who you are. Second, we don't see an accident...
给我听好 老兄 我今天衰毙了
Listen to me, dude, I'm having a really fucked-up, wet, bad fucking day.
你有手机就马上给我
So if you have a cell phone, give it to me now!
我们没手机啦 快放开我
Dude, we don't have a cell phone, so could you just let go of me now? !
那就载我们到另一边
I need you to give me a lift in the other direction.
另一边淹水的情况更严重
It's flooded that way too. It's worse than this.
吉妮 打开后车厢 让他们上车
Ginny, pop the trunk. Let them in.
让他们上车
Let them in.
你好吗?
Hey. How you doing?
- 电话还是不通吗? - 对 你的林肯房车呢?
- Phone still dead? - Yeah. Where's your Lincoln?
在两里路外泡水 另一边也淹大水
Stuck in a run-off two miles down the road. The other way's fucked too.
他们载我跟那位小姐一程
The kids gave us a lift. The girl was stranded.
- 有别的捷径吗? - 她是妓女吗?
- Is there another way out? - Is she a hooker?
到底有没有捷径?
Hey! Is there a back road?
雨这么大 你走不了五百尺
Where do you think the water's going? You wouldn't get 500 feet.
- 那位女士情况怎样? - 我不晓得 他们在四号房
- How's the woman? - I don't know. They're in number 4.
"乱葬冢"
抱歉 这儿不是给人休息的
I'm sorry. We don't rent rooms by the hour.
不好笑 这儿还有吃的吗?
Funny. You still serving food?
转角有一台自动贩卖机 请自便
Vending machines are around the corner. Go ahead.
三十元付现 出示身份证
Rooms are 30 bucks in advance with picture ID. You need one room or two?
你们要一间或两间? 我在跟你讲话 请你看着我
Excuse me. I was talking to you. I'd appreciate it if you looked at me.
我不喜欢看到贱货
Well, I don't like looking at trash.
我们被困在这儿 今晚走不了
We're a little stuck here, George. I don't think we can get out tonight.
- 她一直发抖 - 她休克了
- She just keeps shaking. - She's in shock.
- 让我看看 - 什么?
- Let me take a look. - What?
让我看
Let me take a look.
你太太有带针线盒吗?
Did your wife pack a sewing kit?
没有 没有 No. No.
吉妮 等一下
Ginny, wait up.
六号房
Six.
至少这是幸运号码
At least we got a good number.
- 你有感觉到吗? - 感觉到什么?
- Did you feel that? - Feel what?
一股寒意
Cold.
你是老板吗?
Are you the manager?
是啊
Yeah.
我是看守所的罗德警官 我在押解一名人犯
I'm Officer Rhodes, Corrections. I'm transporting a prisoner here.
你可以拒绝为我们服务
The law gives you the right to refuse us service...
但是淹大水 我想要一间房间
...but the roads are flooded. I could use a room.
- 这是紧急状况 - 你车上有无线电吗?
- It's an emergency. - You got a radio in that car?
- 他是谁? - 他是司机 出了车祸
- Who's this? - Limo driver, had an accident.
有人受重伤 要叫救护车
I got a lady pretty banged up. I could use an ambulance.
442号警车请求医疗协助
Four-four-two requesting medical.
没有讯号 一直都是这样
Nothing. It's been like this for the past hour.
她失血过多 你有急救箱吗?
She's losing a lot of blood. Got a first aid kit?
只有OK绷
Band-Aids, that's it.
- 你有针线吗? - 餐厅搞不好有
- How about a needle and thread? - Maybe in the diner.
我去拿 你别出来
I'll get it. Locked up. Stay dry.
我会给你钥匙 你住十号房
I'll be back with your key. I'll put you in 10.
- 好 谢了 - 那是什么人?
- Okay, thanks. - What do you got back there?
押解人犯
Prison transfer.
你好了以后能不能到四号房?
Maybe when you get him situated, come to 4 and look at the lady.
- 我想请你看看伤患 - 没问题
- I could use a second opinion. - Yeah, sure.
你这下完蛋了
Looks like you're fucked.
闭嘴
Shut up!
- 我没有肉色的线 - 没关系
- I wish I had beige. - This is fine.
肉色会比较好
Would have been better.
我要去招呼那位警官 你有需要的话可以通知我
I gotta get the officer situated. Let me know if you need something.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你从哪儿学会这一套?
Where did you learn to do that?
像你这样边看边学的
Pretty much where you're standing.
那个...
Hey, is the...?
那个小朋友没事吧?
The little boy, is he all right?
车祸后他一句话也没说
He hasn't said a word since the accident.
他没事 他很少说话
No, no, no. He doesn't talk much ever since the...
我是他继父
I'm his stepfather.
他的生父...
His father...
两年前离家出走
Two years ago, he left.
他的脾气不好
Little temper problem.
小心走
Watch your step.
沙发不牢靠
The furniture's for shit.
要嘛就把他铐在马桶上面
If you're fixing to cuff him to something, the toilet's bolted down.
谢谢你的帮忙哦
Thank you so much for your assistance.
- 好主意 来吧 - 我穿着一身囚衣
- It's a good idea. Come on. - I got stripes
我穿着一身囚衣
Stripes around my shoulders And these chains
手铐脚镣真难受
These chains They're about to...
我去看看那位女士
Let's go look at that lady.
- 找到人吗? - 什么?
- You get anyone? - What?
- 无线电接通了吗? - 还没有
- Did you get through? - No, not yet.
你缝合得很好
Good stitch job.
脉搏弱却很稳 尽量让她舒服
Pulse is shallow, but steady. Keep her comfortable.
我们可以轮流用无线电
We should take turns on the radio, if that's all right.
不用了 我可以
No, it's not. I can manage.
警察先生 你要抓我吗?
You gonna arrest me, officer?
什么?
What?
你怎么知道我是警察?
How'd you do that? How'd you know I was a cop?
聪明
No shit.
芝多司当晚餐?
Cheetos for dinner, huh?
- 很不营养哦 - 你有更好的主意吗?
- That don't seem right. - You got a better idea?
我当兵时当过厨子 要是餐厅有开我可以做饭
I worked mess in the service. Maybe the diner's open. I could...
你有铜板吗?
You got change for a dollar?
不晓得 我看看
I don't know. Let me see.
拿去
Here you go.
你叫什么名字?
You got a name?
- 巴黎 - 巴黎?
- Paris. - Paris, huh?
让我来
I'll get it.
我没去过
Never been.
今晚你也别想去
Well, you ain't going tonight.
求求你
Please.
求求你 振作点
Please be strong.
我跟提姆西...
You see, Timothy and I...
我们需要你
...we need you.
我们好需要你
We need you so much.
小路?
Lou?
你要告诉他们在那种环境...
You need to tell them, Harry, that I can't work, I can't perform...
我不能散发我的魅力
...I can't shine living in an environment like that.
这跟片酬无关 完全是工作环境太糟
No, it is not about the money. It's about the working conditions.
一格
One bar.
又没了
No bar.
一格
One bar.
两格
Two bars.
快呀
Come on. Come on.
这就对了
Here we go.
有了 快呀
There you go. Come on.
这什么鬼地方嘛?
Goddamn desert wasteland!
可恶 刚才有讯号
Oh, shit! I just had it.
我的天
Holy fuck.
- 我的妈呀 - 这是谁?
- Jesus, Mother of God. - Who is this?
我负责接送的女人
The woman I was driving.
- 你在干嘛? - 里面有东西
- What the hell are you doing? - There's something in there.
- 用这个 - 谢了
- Use this, man. - Thanks.
- 你也是警察? - 以前是
- Are you a cop? - I was.
- 她住十号房? - 我才是
- She was in Room 10? - I am.
- 你的人犯呢? - 铐在马桶上头
- Where's your guy? - Cuffed to a toilet.
可恶透顶
Son of a bitch.
这一趟路开得好累
That was a fucking drive.
- 各位 - 法官大人
- Gentlemen. - Your Honor.
好了吗? 好吧
Ready, Sharon? Alrighty.
内华达州控告芮佛一案...
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada, for the purposes of...
法官大人 请恕我冒犯 我们应该等被告来了才开始
Judge Taylor, sir, with due respect, we should wait till my client arrives.
- 他有出席的权利 - 他哪来的权利?
- He has a right to be present. - He has precious few rights.
他明天就要被处决
He's 24 hours from execution.
我们要证明他的精神状况...
But to demonstrate his mental state, which is the purpose... His mental state?
他的精神状况?
His mental state?
你知道现在几点吗? 我可没时间听废话
Do you know what time it is? You think I got time for bullshit?
检察官三更半夜打给我 要我重审...
That the justices called me in the middle of the night to review a case...
我已经判决的案子 你也许觉得很高兴
...I already sat on, that I already decided, may make you happy.
但是我却超不爽
But it pisses me off.
等你的被告来了想干什么都行
When your boy gets here, do what you want, but in the name of decency...
你现在有话快说有屁快放
...state your goddamn case!
是的
Yes, sir.
来一杯咖啡 黑咖啡
Somebody get me a cup of coffee, black.
好了 大家听好
All right, everybody! Listen up!
今晚发生了一件意外
There was an incident tonight.
警察的用语就是 有人的脑袋被砍断
That's police talk for, "Someone's head got lopped off."
赖瑞
Larry!
- 卡萝琳苏珊惨遭谋杀 - 什么?
- Caroline Suzanne was murdered. - What?
- 卡萝琳苏珊是谁? - 我负责接送的女明星
- Who's Caroline Suzanne? - The actress I was driving.
她在哪里遇害?
And where exactly did that happen?
我们不清楚 找不到尸体
We don't know, because we can't find the body.
只找到一部份
Not all of it anyway.
- 找不到尸体是什么意思? - 我们只要保持冷静就不会有事
- What do you mean, you can't find it? - Stay calm. Everything will be all right.
押解人犯的罗德警官在外面
Officer Rhodes is outside. He was transporting a convict.
- 他的人犯脱逃了 - 你们在说什么...?
- Who escaped. - What are you... ?
- 冷静点 - 他让犯人逃走了
- Hold on. - Running free!
请你乖乖闭嘴听他说
Will you shut the fuck up so he can talk?
这是我的旅馆 别叫我闭嘴
This is my place, ho! I'll say what I please!
- 这儿很安全 - 才不安全
- It's safe here. - It is not safe here!
- 这儿有警察 - 两个警察
- There's a cop here. - Yeah, two cops.
你也是警察?
You're a cop?
- 我以前是 赖瑞 闭嘴 - 这儿不安全 我要离开...
- I was. Shut up, Larry! - It's not safe here! I'm not staying...
不会有事的
It's all right. It's okay.
没找到
Nothing.
- 她没事吧? - 吉妮
- Is she okay? - Ginny.
拜托你? 冷静点 别这样
Ginny, will you...? Stop it. Don't do this right now.
- 你在干嘛? - 安抚一下你女友
- What are you doing? - Put your arm around your girlfriend.
- 她是我老婆 - 大家都留在这儿
- Actually, she's my wife. - Everybody just stay here.
- 大家都留在这儿 - 慢着 他在我就要走
- Stay in this room. - Wait! I'm not staying here if he is.
- 你留着 - 不行
- Yes, you are. - No, I'm not.
- 我要走 - 好 赖瑞
- I'm not. - All right. Larry?
- 跟我来 - 为什么?
- Come with us. - Why?
- 你对这儿很熟 - 我只知道我不是条子
- You know the place. - Here's what I know. I'm not a cop.
我也不听一个妓女的命令
I don't take orders from a professional slut!
- 去你的 - 请你留下来
- Fuck you! - Listen. Just stay here, please.
让大家保持冷静
Keep everybody calm.
这种天气他走不远的
He's not gonna get too far. Not in this!
罗德!
Rhodes!
罗德 他犯了什么罪?
What are we chasing here?
多重凶杀罪
Multiple homicide.
我到那边去 待会到后面会合
I'll go around this way. Meet you in back.
你是长期定居在赌城吗?
Is that where you live full-time? Las Vegas?
- 以前是 - 那是什么意思?
- Used to. - What's that supposed to mean?
意思是我不住那儿了
It means I don't live there anymore.
"乱葬塚"
缅因?
Maine!
我们用这间厕所 先进去看看
We'll go see if we can use this one. We'll go in here.
不能回房间就用这间吧
Since that wasn't a successful attempt, we'll go in here.
我就在外面 没事的 我守在外面
I'll be right out here. It's okay. I'm gonna stand guard.
放心 我就在这儿哪里也不去
Not a worry. I'll be right here. I'm not going anywhere.
通常都是他妈陪他上厕所
See, his mother usually does this.
你们结婚有多久?
Hey, Ginny. So how long you two been married?
九个钟头前 我们是一时冲动
About nine hours. It was a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing.
赌城万岁 对吧?
Viva Las Vegas, huh, Gin?
- 我们要离开 - 我正在跟她讲话
- We need to leave! - I was just talking to her.
出了事 我一定要离开
Something's happening! I need to get out of here!
- 吉妮! 吉妮! - 我又不是你的人
- Ginny! Ginny! - You don't own me, Lou!
你胜里的小孩有一半是我的
I own what's inside you! Half, at least.
我和我的小孩都不是你的
You don't own any part of me or my baby!
那我干嘛娶你?
Then why did I marry you?
- 别用力甩我门 - 喂! 喂!
- Don't slam the goddamn door on me! - Hey! Hey!
冷静一点
You guys, just calm down!
你不能走 哪儿也去不了
We are not leaving. There is no place else to go.
外面淹大水 给我住手
There's a flood outside, Ginny. Stop it! Stop it!
我没有怀孕
I'm not pregnant!
你说什么?
What did you just say?
我骗你
I lied.
我没有怀孕
I'm not pregnant.
怎么会? 我看到验孕棒
What are you talking about? I saw the test.
你为什么要骗我?
Why would you do that to me?
艾莉森看到你带妹妹去舞厅
Because Alison saw you at The Hawk with that fucking girl!
- 拜托 你是三岁小孩吗? - 走开
- Ginny, what are we, like 15? - Go away!
可恶
Goddamn!
- 给我开门 - 不要
- Open this goddamn door, Ginny! - No!
我有一年没去舞厅了
I haven't been to The Hawk in over a fucking year.
艾莉森那个臭婆娘 只会在背后挑拨离间
Alison is a stupid bitch-whore, who likes fucking with your head.
快开门 吉妮
Open the damn door, Ginny.
- 快开门 - 你要先冷静下来
- Open the fucking door! - Not until you calm down!
我很冷静 我冷静得很
I'm calm! I am very fucking calm!
你想干嘛?
What are you doing?
小路?
Lou?
吉妮 快开门 快开门
Ginny, open this damn door! Open the door!
- 快开门 - 住手
- Open the door! - Stop it, stop it!
吉妮 快给我开门
Ginny, damn it, open the door! Ginny, Ginny, Ginny!
小路 求求你快住手
Lou, please stop!
小路?
Lou?
我的天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
来人呀 快来帮帮我
Help me! Somebody help me!
帮帮我
Help me!
帮帮我 来人呀
Help me! Somebody help me!
他在里面吗?
Is he in there? Is he in there?
你没事吧? 出了什么事?
Ginny, are you okay? What happened? What happened?
- 该死 - 老天爷
- Oh, shit. - Jesus Christ.
小路? 小路?
Lou? Lou?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
汽车旅馆
搞什么?
What the hell?
我靠
Oh, shit!
过来
Come here!
逮到他了 他们逮到他
They caught him. They caught him.
干嘛把他关在这儿?
Why are we keeping him in here?
- 你想关在哪儿? - 我不知道
- Where would you prefer, Larry? - I don't know.
我不是叫你留在房间吗?
I told you to stay in 3, didn't I? Did I tell you that?
他们大吵一架冲出去 我去找他们回来
They got in a fight! I tried to get them to go back inside!
再试试无线电
Should we try the radio again?
赖瑞 留下来看着他
Larry, just stay here and watch him.
- 你回去照顾吉妮 - 你要去哪儿?
- Go back and look after Ginny. - Where are you going?
拜托你去好吗?
Just do it, please.
艾德?
Ed?
我不太会看守犯人耶
I don't know if I'm comfortable with guard duty, per se.
他昏迷不醒 而且被五花大绑
He's unconscious, Larry. He's tied to a post.
提姆西
Timmy.
艾莉丝我的天 艾莉丝?
Alice? Oh, my God. Alice?
我什么都不记得
I don't remember anything.
我们出了车祸
We had an accident
乔治 请你看好吉妮
George? Can you keep an eye on Ginny for a minute?
她醒来了 我要去拿药给她吃
She's awake now. I have to get some aspirin to help her.
我得回房去拿东西
Darling, I gotta go get something out of my room.
- 糟了! - 怎么了?
- Shit! - What's wrong, buddy?
冰箱里有什么?
What do you got in the fridge?
- 闭嘴 - 里面有什么?
- You shut up. - What's in there?
里面到底有什么?
What's in there?
- 你藏了什么? - 给我闭嘴
- What do you got in there? - Shut up.
你藏了什么东西?
What is it, huh?
- 闭嘴 - 尽管告诉我
- Shut up. - You can tell me.
我不会说出去 因为我也有一个大秘密
I'm good at keeping secrets. I got a whopper myself.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
王八蛋
Motherfucker!
- 你在这儿干嘛? - 拿我的东西
- What are you doing out here? - Getting shit that's mine.
你在干嘛? 怎么? 我不能问吗?
What are you doing? What, I don't get to ask a question?
两个人遇害 我在拍照存证
I'm taking photos. There's been two murders. Before all the evidence...
才怪 你只是个司机 你到底想干嘛?
That's not an answer. You're a limo driver. What are you doing?
你想赢一枚英勇司机奖章吗?
Looking to win some "beyond the call of duty," limo-driver merit badge?
你不是警察 不必逞英雄
You're not on the job anymore. You don't need to be a hero.
外面有一个真正的警察...
There's a real, live, active-duty cop outside...
他让一个杀人犯脱逃
The one who's managed to lose a convicted killer?
你这个人很龟毛耶
You're a complicated cat, Edward.
才没有
No. Not really.
我觉得有
I think so.
你几月出生?
What month were you born?
- 五月 - 金牛座
- May. - Taurus.
跟我一样
Same as me.
- 你在哪儿当过差? - 洛杉矶
- Where were you a cop? - Los Angeles.
你是被炒鱿鱼还是辞职不干?
Were you fired or did you quit?
我请长期病假
I took medical leave.
当警察让我生病
It was making me sick.
我猜我是受不了那种压力
I burned out, I guess. Wasn't up for it.
有一天我接到报案...
One day I got a call...
有人想跳楼自杀
...for a jumper.
一个墨西哥裔女生
A young Mexican girl.
她得了爱滋病还怀了身孕
Pregnant, infected with AIDS, totally strung-out.
她真的是走投无路
She was truly one of the doomed.
我请她让我把她抱下来
I asked her to come in off the ledge and into my arms.
她问我她有什么好活的? 活着有什么意义?
She asked me why she should bother living.
你怎么说?
What did you say?
我们受过训练要说一些话
I was trained to tell her lots of things.
像是你要为亲人着想之类的
Her dreams, all the people who'd miss her.
但是我却犹豫了一秒
But for a second, I hesitated.
她看出来了
And she saw it.
在那短短的一秒 我想不出活着有什么意义
Within that second, I couldn't think of one optimistic thing to say to her.
于是她展开双臂 奋力一跳
So she spread her arms and jumped.
我开始会头痛...
I started getting headaches...
后来经常失去意识
...and eventually started blacking out.
所以我就请病假
So I filed for medical.
那是什么?
What?
What is it?
罗德!
Rhodes!
- 更糟 只有杂讯 - 女明星的房间钥匙呢?
- It's worse. Nothing but static! - Where's that key from the actress?
这在那小子身上找到
This was on the kid.
- 这算是倒数吗? - 赖瑞
- What is it, some kind of countdown? - Larry!
他在干什么? 赖瑞 过来
What the fuck is he doing? Larry, come over here!
快过来 你在干嘛?
Come over here, man. What are you doing? Come over here.
- 你在干什么? - 我只是去拿东西
- What are you doing? - I just went to get something.
我们叫你看守人犯 你到办公室干嘛?
We told you to watch the guy. What are you doing in your office?
我只是去拿东西
I just went to get something.
这家旅馆有几副钥匙? 看着我 有几副?
How many sets of keys are there to this place? Look at me. How many?
- 两副 一支万能钥匙 - 我的老天
- Two and a master set. - Oh, my fucking God!
赖瑞 你这大混蛋 混帐东西 给我进来
Larry, you mother... ! You son of a... ! Get the fuck in here! Get in here!
你为什么杀死我的人犯?
Why did you kill him? Why did you kill my con?
哇靠这是谁干的? 人不是我杀的
Holy shit! Who did that? Jesus Christ, I didn't do that!
放屁 你在撒谎
Bullshit! You're lying!
- 那是你的球棒 - 对 但不是我干的
- It's your bat sticking out of his throat! - I know, but I didn't do it!
检查每一道门
Check the doors!
- 不是我干的 - 看看他
- I didn't do it! - Look at him!
- 你干嘛杀他? - 你跑出去干嘛?
- Why'd you kill him? - Why were you outside?
- 你为什么出去? - 我很害怕
- Why'd you leave him? - I was scared.
- 怕什么? - 你们不会明白
- What were you scared of? - You wouldn't understand.
说来听听
Try me.
- 你为什么杀死他? - 我没有
- Why'd you kill my con? - I didn't!
我不知道这是... 我只是回办公室而已
I don't know how... I went to my office, that's all!
- 你干嘛离开? - 这是你的钥匙吗? 八号房?
- Why'd you leave him? - This your key? Number 8?
十九八? 这是你的钥匙
Ten, nine, eight, huh? This is your key!
你不能这么说 这不是我的钥匙
You can't say that! Those aren't my keys!
你这是栽贼耶 你看看
That's like leading the witness or something. Look.
这些才是我的钥匙 你瞧
These are my keys, okay? These are my keys. You see?
这是女明星的古驰钱包
You got a Gucci wallet? It's the actress's.
我是拿了她的钱包 不过是在她死后
Yes, I took her wallet. Afterwards. After she died!
她死了以后 我没杀她 我也没杀他
Afterwards, all right? I didn't kill her. And I didn't kill him.
- 放开她 - 退后 你们别想嫁祸给我
- Let her go, Larry. - Get back! You won't pin this on me.
- 提姆西? - 快把他带走
- Timothy? - Get him out of here!
- 把刀子放下 - 人不是我杀的
- Put it down. - I didn't hurt anybody. No one!
不过我讨厌这婊子 你们敢过来...
But I don't like cheap fucking whores! If you take one more step...
妈的!
Fuck!
快把他弄走
Get it off!
糟糕!
Shit!
臭卡车 快发动呀
Come on, you little bitch. Please fucking start.
- 可恶 - 喂!
- Goddamn it! - Hey!
赖瑞 停车
Larry, stop!
这是怎么回事?
What is going on?
- 赖瑞! - 给我让开 我什么都没做
- Larry! - Get out of my way, I didn't do shit!
提姆西! 提姆西!
Timothy! Timothy!
被告是四级解离性身分病患...
An insanity plea was refused by the court...
法庭却拒绝承认他的精神错乱
...despite the fact that my client is a certifiable Axis IV dissociative.
他到现在对他所犯的罪 都毫不知情
To this day, he remains unaware of the crimes for which he was convicted.
1986年最高法院判决...
In 1986, the Supreme Court ruled decisively that states cannot execute...
州政府不能处决精神错乱人犯
...a person who does not understand why he's being put to death.
他签下自白书
He signed a confession.
- 那是他亲口对我说的供词 - 还有...
- He didn't just sign it, he dictated it. - Thirdly...
这是麦肯的日记 被藏在物证室
...Malcolm's diaries found misfiled in state evidence.
这上面有他在命案前的记录
this notebook contains entries made just before the murders.
重点是他的笔迹有很大的改变
Important to note are the spectacular changes in handwriting style...
还有语调和观点
...tone, point of view.
这是多重人格的内心世界
What you are looking at are the private thoughts of several different people.
请让马医师进一步说明
With permission, Dr. Mallick will elaborate.
谢谢你
Thank you.
法官大人 解离性身分 也就是多重人格...
Your Honor, there is no universally efficacious treatment...
并没有有效的治疗方法
...for Dissociative Identity Disorder.
我只能试着整合这些多重人格
In theory, one attempts to move the patient towards integration.
- 让病患破碎的心灵愈合 - 法官大人
- A folding of their fractured psyche. - Your Honor?
他来了
He's here.
这只是场意外
No! What you saw was an accident!
他突然冲出来 我没有杀人
He ran out in front of me! I'm not a murderer!
冷冻库有一具尸体
There's a dead body in your freezer, Larry.
- 我发现他死了 我没杀他 - 少来了
- I didn't kill him. I found him like that. - Stop it!
求求你们听我说 上个月我在赌城输个精光
Listen! Listen! I was in Vegas last month and I lost everything, okay?
输个精光
Everything!
我走投无路只好往西走
I drove west. I didn't know where to go, but I was running on empty...
我的车没油了只好来这儿
...so I pulled in here at this place.
加油站没人 所以我就直接...
And there was no one at the station, so I came over to the office...
走进办公室
...and I walked in.
老板就坐在办公桌
And there, sitting at that desk right there, was the manager...
一头栽进冷冻披萨暴毙
...facedown in a Banquet Potpie. Dead!
- 他一定是心脏病发作 - 这未免太扯了
- Heart attack or something. - Banquet Potpie!
天晓得他死了有多久
He'd been sitting there for God knows how long.
这时候突然有一个人来住房
All of a sudden, this auto-parts salesman pulls up, looking for a room.
当时我身无分文...
I didn't have a fucking dime...
所以就收了三十元给他房间
...so I took his 30 and gave him one.
我拿了钥匙给他一间房间
I just took the key from the wall and gave him a room.
也许我那么做不对 但是我没钱 只好那么做
Maybe that was wrong, but I was broke, and that's what I did.
然后我就回办公室
Then I came back in here...
抬走赖瑞的尸体 他也叫赖瑞
...and I moved Larry's body... His name was Larry too.
然后把他放进冷冻库
I put him in the freezer.
天气很热 我不想让他发臭
I wasn't trying to hide him. It was hot out.
我只想等他的家人来找他
I thought it was the best place for him till his family or someone came along.
他的家人没找上门...
Only no one did...
客人却络绎不绝
...except more guests.
我只好让他们住进来
So I checked them in too.
他们都很满意
And they all seemed happy...
所以我就待了下来
...so I just stayed.
省省吧 这全是胡扯淡
Cry me a river. This is a total crock of shit!
- 才不是 - 承认吧 你杀死他
- No, it's not! - Admit it, you killed him!
你也杀死人犯她老公...
Just like you killed my con. Just like you killed her husband.
和他的女明星 承认吧
Just like you killed his actress. Just admit it.
- 说"人是我杀的" - 别说了 他受不了了
- Say it, "I killed them." - Stop it! He can't take any more!
没事了 我们抓到凶手了
Everything is okay now. Everything is fine. We got the guy. It's fine.
- 我不能确定 - 什么?
- I don't know what we got. - What?
两小时前也以为抓到凶手...
We thought we got the guy two hours ago, then...
拜托 凶手就是这家伙
You believe this shit? It's him! It's this guy!
他拿刀威胁你 记得吗?
He had a knife to your neck, remember?
这故事太夸张 搞不好是真的
His story's so unbelievable, I think it just might be true.
她说的有道理
She's got a point.
你们都疯了
You guys are crazy.
也许是因为这儿是乱葬塚
Maybe it's the burial ground.
什么?
What?
这地方全都是墓地
Read the brochure in there. It's all around us.
一百年前印第安人被迫迁移
A hundred years ago, the government moved these Indians here.
这儿缺水他们全都渴死
They all died because there was no water.
所以他们就回来报仇吗?
Now they're coming back to life like sea monkeys, huh?
这太扯了 小姑娘
Come on. Give me a break, sweetheart.
- 别这样 罗德 - 你才别这样
- Just take it easy, Rhodes. - You know, you take it easy!
你从一开始就在发号施令
You've tried to run this show all night. Giving orders, pointing fingers!
你还把错归在我的人犯头上 结果他也挂了
You blamed my con for everything, and he ends up dead.
我告诉你 凶手就是他 大家都看到他撞死乔治
I'm telling you, it's him! We all saw him run down George.
他偷走的钱包在那儿
Your actress's wallet is right there. She's dead, there's the wallet.
- 这还不够吗? - 住嘴 别说了
- What more do you want? - Stop it! Please shut up!
我告诉你们该怎么做
All right. You want a plan? Here's the plan, okay?
谁也别乱跑 我们都待在这儿等天亮
No one's gonna move. We'll stay here, like this, in this room until dawn.
没有人可以离开
No one leaves, no one moves.
他敢乱来我就毙了他
And if he tries anything, I'm gonna shoot him!
有什么想闯进来我也毙了它
And if something out there comes in here, I'll shoot it!
你们想造反我也毙了你们
And if anyone of us tries anything, I'll shoot them!
- 我们懂了 - 很好
- We get it. - Good!
提姆西? 提姆西?
Timmy? Timmy?
- 你要留在这儿 - 没关系
- You need to stay in here with us. - It's all right.
有一部电影拍十个人流落荒岛...
Remember that movie where the 10 strangers went to an island...
他们一个接一个死去
...and then they all died one by one...
结果他们都有一个共通点
...and then it turned out they weren't strangers, they all had a connection?
被他们害的人回来找他们算帐
They all messed with the wrong guy, and he was getting revenge.
闭嘴
Shut up!
也许我们也有共通点
I'm just saying maybe there's a connection between all of us.
像是什么?
Like what?
- 我们都在内华达州 - 闭嘴
- We're all in Nevada. - Shut up!
你打算把人犯押解到哪儿?
Where were you going with your con when you pulled in here?
卡森市
Carson City. Okay?
我要回佛州老家 你呢?
I was going home to Florida. Where were you going?
我要载女明星到洛杉矶
I was taking the actress to L.A.
我在佛州出生
I was born in Florida.
你是凶手 给我乖乖闭嘴
Since you been in that chair, no one's died, so shut up!
谁都可能是凶手
No one's died since we've all been here!
- 小乖乖 坐下来 - 佛州的哪儿?
- Hey, sweetie, sit down. - Where in Florida, Larry?
- 你在哪儿出生? - 你们突然变成好友了吗?
- Where in Florida? - Friends now, huh? Great.
- 波克郡 - 我也是
- Polk County. - That's where I was born.
- 哪一个城镇? - 桑树镇
- Which town? - Mulberry.
- 我是防霜镇 - 怪不得你会离开
- Frostproof. - No wonder you left.
有个小镇叫防霜?
There's a town called Frostproof?
那儿种柳橙 防霜也是小镇的宣传口号
They grow oranges. The name doubles as a slogan.
我巴不得离开 你干嘛回去?
I danced hallelujah the day I left Polk. Why would you wanna go back?
我找到一片果园要出售
I found a grove for sale on the Internet.
有一千两百棵莱姆和柳橙树
Nine acres, 1200 trees. Limes and oranges.
仲介跟我说土壤需要磷...
According to the realtor, the soil needs a few tills, phosphorous...
也要除除草 不过那块地很不错
...lanes need reading, but it's real good land.
怎么了?
What?
听起来很好
It sounds nice.
艾德?
Ed?
她死了
She's dead.
把他带出去
Get him out of here.
来吧 小乖乖
Come on. Come on, sweetie.
你看
Look at this.
- 在哪儿找到的? - 就在地上
- Where'd you get that? - Right here.
一点都没道理 她死于意外
This doesn't make any sense. She died from an accident.
乔治也是死于意外 如果你相信赖瑞的话
George was an accident, if you believe Larry.
七号钥匙呢?
Where is seven?
倒车
Back it up!
- 我就说凶手不是我 - 不可能
- See, I told you it wasn't me! - That's not possible.
我就站在那儿 我们都亲眼看到发生什么事
I was standing right there. I saw what happened. We all saw what happened.
他突然冲出来 没有人料得到
He ran out. Nobody could have known he was gonna do that.
凶手不是人
No one human.
又来了 凶手是恶灵
We're back to that again? It's the spirits, huh?
也许是冷冻库那家伙的冤魂
Maybe it's the ghost of the guy that Larry put in the freezer.
快把我解开
Somebody untie me. Goddamn it!
凶手不是我
You know it wasn't me. Come on.
- 听好 - 我们得离开... - 听好 - 我们得离开... - Listen.
- We gotta get out... - Listen. - We gotta get out...
你跟她带着孩子快走
Take her car and get out. You, her and the kid.
我们无处可去
There's nowhere to go.
- 你的车剩多少油? - 半缸油
- How much gas do you have? - Half a tank.
那就够开到天亮
You can drive till dawn on that. Look at me.
碰到淹水就往另一头开
When you get to where it's flooded, go the other way.
我办不到
I don't know if I can.
带着孩子快走吧
Get the kid and go. Right now. Come on.
提姆
Timmy.
提姆 我们走
Timmy, come on. Let's go. Get up.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
- 他们不能走 - 这边走
- They can't leave! - This way.
大雨过后再见
We'll see you when the storm breaks.
他们不能走 给我回来
Hey! Hey! They can't leave! Where are they going? Get back here!
他们非走不可 快走吧
Go, go, go! They're leaving.
- 他们不能离开 - 走吧!
- They're not leaving. - Go!
在四个人死了之后 你不能让嫌犯脱逃
You can't let suspects leave after four people have been killed!
- 你真的认为他们是嫌犯吗? - 他们不能走
- You really think they're suspects? - They're not leaving!
妈的
Shit.
吉妮!
Ginny!
灭火器 这儿有灭火器吗?
Extinguishers. Larry, you got a fire extinguisher?
- 灭火器在哪儿? - 后面
- Fire extinguisher! Where? - Back there!
车上没有人
Nobody in there.
也许他们都被火化了
Maybe it got so hot, they got cremated.
那也会留下骨灰
There'd be something left.
这是你的错
You did this.
你叫他们上车
You did this! You told them to get into the car!
高兴了吗?
Are you happy?
他的尸体呢?
Where is he?
什么也没有
Nothing.
我投降
I give up!
我投降 你到底想要什么?
I give up! What the hell do you want?
你这大变态 你要我们怎样?
What do you want, you sick bastard? What the fuck do you want from us?
我下礼拜就满三十岁 我只想回老家...
I am turning 30 next week and I just want to go home...
种柳丁
...and grow oranges!
你下礼拜生日?
It's my birthday next week. The 10th.
我也一样 五月十日
我也是
Me too.
我也一样
我也是
Yeah.
乔治约克 五月十日
George York, May 10.
艾莉丝约克 五月十日
Alice York, May 10.
卡萝琳苏珊 五月十日
Caroline Suzanne, May 10
吉妮和路易西安那 五月十日
Ginny and Lou Isiana, May 10.
我赖瑞华盛顿 五月十日
Me, Larry Washington, May fucking 10.
这只有十兆分之一的机率
What are the odds? Must be 10 trillion-to-one.
怎么了?
What is it?
- 电箱在哪里? - 旅馆的另一边
- Where's the fuse box, Larry? - Other side of the building.
吉妮和路易西安那
Ginny and Lou Isiana.
维吉尼亚和路易西安那
Virginia and Louisiana.
卡萝琳...卡罗莱纳
Caroline, Carolina.
巴黎内华达
Paris Nevada
乔治约克
George York.
赖瑞华盛顿
Larry Washington.
罗德...罗德岛
Rhodes, Rhode Island.
艾德达科塔
Ed Dakota.
当我走上楼梯 我看到一个不在那儿的人
When I was going up the stairs I met a man who wasn't there
今天他又不在那里
He wasn't there again today
我希望他会永远消失
I wish I wish he'd go away
你是谁?
Who is this?
我现在跟谁讲话?
Who am I speaking to right now?
那首诗是哪儿学来的?
Where did you learn that poem?
我在跟谁讲话?
Who am I speaking to? Look at me.
看着我 你现在是谁?
Who am I speaking to right now?
医生?
Doc?
- 艾德华? - 发生什么事?
- Edward? - What's happening?
- 安静 - 他听得到我们说话?
- Please be quiet. - He can hear what we're saying?
我当然听得到你说话
Of course I can hear what you're fucking saying.
你爽约了 你跑去哪儿?
Edward, you missed your last appointment. Where have you been?
- 我又失去意识吗? - 仔细想
- Did I black out again? - Try and think back.
你在哪里?
Where have you been?
我开车送一个女明星...
All right. I was driving this actress...
我们被困在汽车旅馆 有一场暴风雨
...and we got stuck at the motel. There was a storm.
我们被暴风雨困住出不去
We couldn't get out because of the storm.
那儿发生什么事?
What happened at the motel?
大家一个一个死去
People started dying.
这没有道理 他们的尸体...
And then their bodies... It didn't make any sense.
全都消失不见
They disappeared.
我要给你看一样东西
Edward, I'd like to show something to you, if I may.
你认得这个人吗?
Do you recognize this man?
不认得
No.
他是麦肯芮佛
That man, Edward, is Malcolm Rivers.
他的一生很坎坷 他四年前...
He's had a very troubled life. He was arrested four years ago...
残暴地夺走六条人命 所以被捕入狱
...and convicted of the murder of six people in a violent rampage.
- 这是他干的 - 警探 别这样
- He did this. - Detective, please.
艾德华 听我说
Edward, listen to me.
当一个小孩遭受重大打击 他的心灵会严重受创...
When faced with an intense trauma, a child's mind may fracture...
造成人格的分裂
...creating disassociated identities.
这就是麦肯芮佛的遭遇
That's exactly what happened to Malcolm Rivers.
他有一般人所谓的...
He developed a condition that is commonly known...
多重人格症
...as Multiple Personality Syndrome.
你为什么跟我说这些?
Why are you telling me this?
因为你...
Because you, Edward...
是他多重人格中的一个
...are one of his personalities.
什么?
What?
老天 你把我的脸怎么了?
Jesus Christ! What the fuck did you do to my face?
- 冷静下来 - 我的脸呢?
- Keep calm. - Where is my face?
- 这就是你的脸 - 我为什么被绑起来?
- That is your face. - Why am I tied up?
- 冷静点 - 我的脸呢?
- Keep calm. - Where is... ?
- 请冷静 - 天啊
- Please. - Jesus Christ!
- 我的脸呢? - 保持冷静
- Where is my face? - Stay calm.
我才不要保持冷静 我为什么被绑起来?
No! I'm not gonna stay calm! Why am I tied up like this?
这些人是谁? 汽车旅馆发生什么事?
Who are all these people? What happened at the motel?
- 他们人呢? - 他们并不存在
- Where is everybody? - They don't exist, Edward.
你们是麦肯小时候分裂的人格
You were all created by Malcolm as a child.
- 你在骗人 - 想想你知道的
- You're a liar! - Consider what you know.
- 每个人的姓氏都是美国州名 - 不
- Everyone named after a state. - No.
每个人都同一天生日 你也经常失去意识
Everyone sharing the same birthday. Your blackouts.
我当过警察
No! I was a cop!
我在洛杉矶当过六年警察
I was a cop in the Rampart Division of L.A.P.D. for six years.
冷静下来
Edward, please.
我住在好莱坞的公寓大楼
I live in Hollywood, in a studio apartment.
- 你不住在那儿 - 我住在那儿
- You don't live there. - I do live there!
你根本不存在
You don't live anywhere.
我知道你很难接受 但是你在镜子中看到的脸
I know this is difficult to accept, but the face you saw in that mirror...
也就是你巴黎赖瑞...
...is the face I've always seen when I talk to Edward or Paris or Larry...
和你今晚遇到每一个人的脸
...or anyone else you've met tonight.
麦肯正在接受药物治疗
Malcolm is in the midst of a medical treatment.
他的多重人格被迫互相面对
One which forces all his identities to confront one another for the first time.
我知道一定会有暴力行为
I knew there would be violence...
但是他的多重人格也会减少
...and with it, the number of the identities would be reduced.
减少?
Reduced?
今晚你见到的人格...
One of the personalities you've met tonight, Edward...
其中有一个在四年前杀人
...committed those murders four years ago.
他跟你一样控制麦肯的身体
He took control of Malcolm's body, as you have now...
然后犯下残暴的谋杀案 十九个小时后...
...and released an unspeakable rage. And in 19 hours...
麦肯将为这些行为被处决
...Malcolm Rivers will be put to death because of those actions...
除非我能说服这个人...
...unless I can convince that man...
凶手已经消失
...that the killer is gone.
你不行转换人格 艾德华
I need you to stay with me. Edward?
我要你帮我 我要你帮我完成这件事
I need your help. I need your help to finish this.
艾德华 听好
Edward, listen to me.
艾德华 不要转换人格
Edward, stay with me.
听好 我要你明白
Listen to me. I need you to understand.
你不能让凶手活下去
The killer cannot survive.
艾德华!
Edward!
好了吗?
Got it?
我看不见 你有手电筒吗?
I can't see a thing. Is there a flashlight?
等一下
Hang on. Hang on.
- 手电筒呢? - 来了啦 该死
- You got a flashlight? - Yeah, yeah, it's dead. Goddamn it.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我要穿什么?
Hey. What am I supposed to wear, man?
就穿你这身囚衣
You're in it.
赖瑞
Larry.
赖瑞 过来
Larry, come here.
艾德!
Ed!
赖瑞!
Larry!
- 赖瑞! - 巴黎
- Larry! - Paris.
巴黎
Paris.
赖瑞?
Larry?
赖瑞? 赖瑞?
Larry? Larry?
卡车的钥匙呢?
Where are the keys to the truck?
卡车钥匙呢?
- 干得好 - 我们得快走
- That was good, Larry. - We gotta get out of here.
- 卡车钥匙在艾德那儿 - 我有备用钥匙
- Ed has the keys to the truck. - I got a spare right here.
- 他人呢? - 我不知道 拿去
- Where is he? - I don't know. Here.
- 你在干嘛? - 我们需要一把枪
- What are you doing? - We need a gun.
妈的!
Holy shit!
把钥匙给我
Give me the keys to the truck.
艾德!
Ed!
我们得快走
We gotta get out of here!
- 巴黎... - 他追来了...
- Paris... - He's coming. He's...
- 留下来 - 不 你想干嘛?
- Stay here. - What's wrong with you?
巴黎 听我说
Paris, listen to me.
留下来
Stay here.
不会有事的
It's gonna be okay.
把钥匙丢给我
Throw me the keys to the truck, Ed.
把钥匙丢给我 别过来
Throw me the keys to the truck. Stay there. Stay there!
艾德! 艾德! 艾德!
Ed! Ed! Ed!
艾德 让我看
Ed, let me see.
我要送你到医院
We gotta get you to a hospital.
我要送你到医院 知道吗?
We're gonna get you to a hospital, okay?
撑着点 我扶你上车
Stay with me because I'm gonna get you to the truck.
手搭住我的肩 抓紧了
Put your arm around my neck. You gotta hold on, okay?
跟我合作 一二三
You with me, Ed? Stay with me. Okay. One, two, three.
让我扶你起来 你要用力
You gotta help me get you up. Ed, you gotta push a little bit.
你为什么不让我帮你?
Ed, why won't you let me help you?
你去了哪儿?
Where did you go before?
看到什么? 你看到什么?
What did you see? Tell me what you saw.
我看到你
I saw you.
我看到你在柳橙果园
I saw you in an orange grove.
你为什么不让我帮你?
Why won't you let me help you?
你去了哪儿?
Where did you go?
看到什么?
What did you see?
我看到你
I saw you...
你在柳橙果园
...in an orange grove.
问题是该惩罚身体或心灵
The question, Your Honor, is whether to convict the body or the mind.
他的身体的确犯下这些命案
His body committed these murders, that is true.
但是他体内的人格是无辜的
The person who remains inside did not.
泰勒法官 这不见得是真的...
Judge Taylor, that may not be true...
我们今晚看到十个人格被摧毁
We witnessed the destruction of 10 identities tonight.
其中九个有罪 一个是无辜的
Nine were innocent and one was guilty.
他们不是真的
They're not real!
他内心的暴力因子已被消灭
The violence that existed in him has been executed.
你应该让麦肯住进州立疗养院
Your Honor, Malcolm belongs in a state hospital.
内华达州控告芮佛一案...
In the matter of Rivers v. Nevada, it is the recommendation of this court...
本庭建议延缓处决芮佛
...that Mr. Rivers' execution be stayed.
我要把他转到州立精神疗养院
I am transferring Mr. Rivers to state psychiatric services...
交给马医师治疗
...under the care of Dr. Mallick.
你穿破的高跟鞋仿佛在耻笑我
Cracked heels and washed-out horns Blow into my face with scorn
但是我却不愿失去你
But it's not that way I wasn't born to lose you
我要你...
I want you
我急切地要你
I want you so bad
提米
Timmy.
不 求求你不要
不
No, please don't.
提米 求求你...
No, Timmy, please.
怎么了? 麦肯
What is it, Malcolm?
麦肯
Malcolm?
妓女没有...
Whores don't
第二次机会
get a second chance.
当我走上楼梯 我看到一个不在那儿的人
When I was going up the stairs I met a man who wasn't there
今天他又不在那里
He wasn't there again today
我希望他会永远消失
I wish I wish he'd go away